Guide to the Thelma Z. Lavine papers, 1932-2007
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 4: Audio/Visual, 1969-1996; (10 boxes)
  - Various, Women of Achievement, WETA-FM Rebroadcast, 1:00 pm, February 10, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Various, Women of Achievement, WETA-FM Rebroadcast, 4:30 pm, February 10, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Various, Romantic Movement, January 26, 1983 (Box 40)
    Th. Lavine GWU for Smithsonian
  - Various, Copy #1, August 27, 1985 (Box 40)
    LECTURER Dr. Thelma Z. Lavine / LANGUAGE & CHANNEL Floor Reel ONE / SIDE ONE Lecture Part 1 / SIDE TWO Lecture Part 2
  - Various, Copy #1, August 27, 1985 (Box 40)
    LECTURER DR. Thelma Z. Lavine / LANGUAGE & CHANNEL Floor Reel Two / SIDE ONE Q&A
  - Various, Interpretation, Human Agency, and Economics, March 28, 1986 (Box 40)
    Side A - SIE conference Vol I / Jack High (introduction) Thelma Lavine (Beg.) Ralph Rector Side B - Thelma Lavine (conclusion), Don Lavoie, Discussion (Beg)
  - Various, Dr. Thelma Lavine: Robinson Lecture, April 9, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Various, 1-A Phil & Lit Theory / 1-B, September 11, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Various, 2, 2A, September 18, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Various, Service for Gertrude, June 3, 1990 (Box 40)
  - Various, 1992 Hurst Lecture, March 25, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Various, Sophie's World (interview), September 30, 1994 (Box 40)
  - Various, TZL, A1 & B1, January 1, 1996 (Box 40)
  - Various, TZL, 2A & 2B, January 1, 1996 (Box 40)
  - Various, Diane Rehm show on Freud, A & B, 6, January 8, 1996 (Box 40)
  - Various, 9, July 13, 1996 (Box 40)
    000-400 / 400-480 / A 000-150 TZL / B
  - Various, TZL IA & IB, undated (Box 40)
  - Various, Program 4, Plato 3, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, (2) TZL, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, B TZL 3, 9/30, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Dec 5, Phil, 25, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Oct. 2 Side 1 / Side 2, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Oct 11, Side 1 / Side 2, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Oct 23, Side 1 / Side 2, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Sunday Scholar, March 16, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Phil, Dec 8, 26/8, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 11/8 phil, undated (Box 41)
    Side A - Hegel cont'd Side B - "Trinity" "Absolute" Dialectic
  - Various, undated (Box 41)
    Side 1 - BLEECKER ST. PLAYERS / Kainer, R: Interview WAMU Side 2 - PHILOSOPHY OF PSYCHOTHERAPY / WEIGERT: Separation-Individuation
  - Various, 76a Nelly Caplan; Papa / 76b do. tr. 2, undated (Box 41)
    As identified on case.
  - Various, 3, 9/18, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 4, 9/25, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 5, 9/25 & 10/2, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 7, 10/9, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 8, 10/9, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 9, 10/16, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 10, 10/16 & 10/23, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 11, 10/23, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 12, 10/30, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 13, 10/30, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 13, 11/6, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 14, 11/6, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 15, 11/13, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 16, one of two 11/20, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 18, 12/4, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 20, (A) and 12 (B), undated (Box 41)
    Side A - 20 12/11 Side B - 12 11/4 ->11/11
  - Various, 21, 12/11, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, NY: / LM,NY&DG, undated (Box 41)
  - Various, Mastering Your Feelings, by David Viscott, M.D., undated (Box 41)
  - Various, 52 Minutes to Turn Your Life Around, by David Viscott, M.D., undated (Box 41)
  - Various, United States Holocaust Memorial Museum, Mike Lerman, Narrator, 1992 (Box 41)
    "Witnesses to the Holocaust." date given is (c) date.
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 41)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 41)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, no case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Unidentified, with case, undated (Box 42)
  - Photograph, Eliade, May 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    "May 1987" is stamped on back, appears to be from printing service - exact date photo was taken is unknown.
  - Photograph, First United Methodist group, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Thelma Z. Lavine in college uniform, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Photograph of TZL in a college uniform as part of a group promoting "GOOD HEALTH + GOOD FACULTIES." TZL is on the left looking to her left.
  - Photograph, set of MPT television show, 1980s (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Reel to reel magnetic tape, unidentified, undated (Box 43)
  - Videocassette, CSMP Conference, March 28, 1986 (Box 43)
  - Videocassette, unidentified, undated (Box 43)